(Sheldon:)When I opened the door,
(Sheldon:)I saw my father having relations
with another woman.
Oh, that's awful!
I know.
(Sheldon:)It's also why
I never open a door
(Sheldon:)without knocking three times.
(Sheldon:)I mean, the first
one's traditional,
but two and three are for people
to get their pants on.
(Penny:)Well, what happened
with your dad?
(Sheldon:)We locked eyes,
I ran to my room,
(Sheldon:)and we never, ever spoke of it.
(Penny:)You poor thing.
(Sheldon:)Since Amy and I
have been living together,
(Sheldon:)we've been bickering
like my parents used to.
(Penny:)And you're afraid you're gonna
do something like your dad did?
(Sheldon:)Yes. I need to prepare her now
(Sheldon:)to save her from pain
down the road.
(Penny:)Down the road?
(Penny:)Sheldon, she wanted to share a
toothbrush holder with you,
(Penny:)and now you're at an ice cream
parlor trying to pick up women!
(Sheldon:)Well, anything can sound silly
when you put it in that tone.
(Penny:)Honey, instead of
worrying about pain
(Penny:)you might cause in the
future, how about trying